silhouettelift.com 2012-10-18

# Silhouette Lift | Privacy Policy

Silhouette Lift, Inc. (“Silhouette Lift”) values your privacy and the privacy of our other customers and visitors to our website (the “Website”). Visitors to the Website are, collectively, referred to herein as “Users” or “you.”

This Privacy Notice describes what information Silhouette Lift gathers from you via the Website, how we use that information, and what we do to protect it.

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the Silhouette Lift [ ****](http://www.merzaesthetics.com/en-US/patient-safety/legal.cfm#terms) **[Terms of Use](http://www.silhouettelift.com/terms-of-use/ "Terms of Use")** . Your use of the Website and any personally identifiable information you provide on the Website are subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and Silhouette Lift Terms of Use.

## The Information Silhouette Lift Collects:

  * **User-provided Information:** You may provide to Silhouette Lift personally identifiable information (such as your name, email address, mailing address, zip code, telephone number, or fax number) when using the Website. For example, if you use the Website to find doctors in your area, we will ask for your address and/or zip code, so that we can provide a list of local doctors who have experience in using Silhouette Lift. You may also provide personally identifiable information if you [contact](http://www.silhouettelift.com/contact/ "contact") us through the Website with questions or comments.

  * **“Automatically Collected” Non-Personally Identifiable Information:** When you visit the Website, we may automatically record certain information from your web browser by using various types of technology, including “cookies.” This “automatically collected” information may include Internet Protocol address (“ **IP Address** “), web browser type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after the Website, the pages and Materials you view on the Website, and the dates and times that you visit the Website.

## The Way Silhouette Lift Uses Information

  * Silhouette Lift uses the information you provide or that we collect, including personally identifiable information, to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide features, information, products, and services, including those found on the Website. We will use your personally identifiable information to manage our business, respond to your requests, and process your transactions, for other customer service purposes, and to address any issues related to legal violations, such as intellectual property infringement, rights of privacy, or defamation.

  * Silhouette Lift uses User information, including “automatically collected” information and “cookies to understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences of visitors to the Website, to improve the way the Website work and look, and to create and enhance features and functionality. For example, the use of “cookies” allows us to remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Website.

  * Silhouette Lift will not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send promotional messages to you unless you have opted in, requested that Silhouette Lift contact you [about Silhouette Lift](http://www.silhouettelift.com/about-silhouette-lift/ "about Silhouette Lift") products and services or other information.

## When Silhouette Lift Discloses Information

  * Silhouette Lift does not sell, trade, rent, or share your personally identifiable information with third party organizations other than our affiliates for their marketing or promotional uses without your express consent or opt-in or unless you request additional information. For example, we will send your contact information to physicians in our network if you request to receive additional information from them. Our affiliates that receive your information may use it to offer products and services to you.

  * Silhouette Lift may disclose non-personally-identifiable information in de-identified or aggregated form to third parties for the purpose of understanding or analyzing the usage, viewing, and demographic patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Website and for similar types of research and analysis.

  * Silhouette Lift may share User information with authorized third party service providers that perform services for us and our affiliates to help us manage our business and provide goods and services to our customers. For example, we may use service providers to host, maintain, and operate the Website, send communications, conduct research, manage and analyze data, and perform other services for us. If we share your personally identifiable information with third-party service providers, we do not authorize them to use or disclose it for any purpose other than the intended purpose.

  * Silhouette Lift may transfer or assign the information that we have collected from Users as part of a corporate reorganization, merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control (including any transfers made as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings) involving all or part of Silhouette Lift.

  * Silhouette Lift may disclose User information, including personally identifiable information, if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant. In some cases, we may make such disclosures without first providing notice to Users.

  * Silhouette Lift also reserves the right to disclose User information, including personally identifiable information, that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to protect our rights or the rights of others, to protect and avert harm to persons or property, or to enforce our Terms of Use or this Privacy Notice.

## Your Choices

If you do not want your personally identifiable information to be used or transferred to third parties as set forth in this Privacy Notice, you may send an email to  **[unsubscribe@silhouettelift.com](mailto:unsubscribe@silhouettelift.com)** .

Please note that, if we are unable to use or share your personally identifiable information as set forth in this Privacy Notice, Silhouette Lift will not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality found on the Website.

For California Residents, California Privacy Rights under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84

California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84 give California residents the right to ask us for a notice describing the categories of personally identifiable information we share with third parties or affiliates for their direct marketing purposes. The notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it has been shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to info@silhouettelift.com or Legal Dept, Silhouette Lift, Inc., 1 technology Drive, Suite F 211, Irvine CA 92618. Please allow 30 days for a response.

## Updating, Correcting, or Removing Personally Identifiable Information

Silhouette Lift strives to keep your information accurate, complete, and current. If you wish to update, correct, or delete your personally identifiable information, you may write to us at info@silhouettelift.com or Customer Service, Silhouette Lift, Inc., 1 technology Drive, Suite F 211, Irvine CA 92618.

Upon receipt of a request to delete personally identifiable information, we will delete the applicable personally identifiable information from our active databases, although your personally identifiable information may continue to be stored on our back-up media.

## Children’s Privacy

Silhouette Lift does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information on Website from persons under 18 years-of-age, and no part of the Website is directed to persons under 18.

## Data Security

Silhouette Lift uses commercially reasonable physical, administrative, and technical safeguards that we believe are designed to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. However, please note that because no security program is impenetrable and criminals have proven apt at circumventing widely-adopted security safeguards, we cannot guarantee that your personally identifiable information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards or any other method.

## Changes and Updates to this Privacy Notice

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically without further notice to you and this will be reflected by a “last modified” date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the Website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.

## Effective Date

This Privacy Notice is effective as of June 6, 2011.

## Silhouette Lift Contact Information

Please contact Silhouette Lift with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, our third-party disclosure practices, or your consent choices at **:**[info@silhouettelift.com](mailto:info@silhouettelift.com) **.**
